http://www.a-p.com/privacy-policy

MENU
AboutPortfolioCareersContact
AboutPortfolioCareersContact
Privacy Policy
Adolfson & Peterson Construction recognizes that privacy is a primary concern for Internet users. To protect your privacy, we do not sell, share, or rent your personal information in any way.
The Information We Collect
Personal Information
We do not collect any personal information from you automatically. The only way we currently receive personal information is if you send it to us through e-mail or through signing up for our newsletter. We do not share, rent, or sell your personal information to anyone.
User Content
User Content is considered any communication you may have with Adolfson & Peterson. For example, you may e-mail us your suggestions or request our newsletter. Adolfson & Peterson Construction may collect User Content, but we will not share, rent, or sell this information.
Opt-In Data
We also collect opt-in data. Opt-in data simply means that if you decide to receive one of our online newsletters, or complete an online survey, we will track which features you have opted to participate in. This information may be used in aggregate and does not personally identify you. Opt-in data helps us tailor content to our readers’ needs.
Other Privacy Practices
Links
Our website contains links to other Web sites that may have different and even conflicting privacy policies from ours. We do our best to link to responsible sites, but we are not responsible for the privacy practices of these sites.
Children’s Privacy
Although our site is a general audience web site that is not specifically designed for or targeted at children, the protection and safety of children is very important to Adolfson & Peterson Construction and we therefore encourage parents and guardians to participate in and supervise the online activities of their children.
We do not knowingly collect, use or disseminate any personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. If, however, we become aware that personally identifiable information regarding a child under the age of 13 has been collected at our site, we will use such information for the sole purpose of contacting a parent or guardian of the child to obtain verifiable parental consent. If we cannot obtain consent after a reasonable period of time, or if when contacted a parent or guardian requests that we do not use or maintain such information, we will delete it from our records. Upon request by a parent or guardian, we will provide a description of the specific types of personal information collected from a child who is under the age of 13.
Public Information
Any information that you disclose in one of our discussion groups is considered public information. You should always be careful when posting personal information that other users will see. Personal Information Changes
You may, at any time, review, update, or change your personal information by emailing or calling us.
Privacy Policy Updates and Changes
We reserve the right, at any time and without notice, to add to, change, update, or modify this Privacy Policy simply by posting the change on the Web site. Any changes will become effective as soon as they are posted.
Confidentiality and Security of Personal Information
We will not collect or share information in any way that has not been covered in our Privacy Policy. We may need to disclose your personal information to comply with a court order or other legal process, to protect our rights or property, to enforce our Web site policies, or to protect the personal safety of users or the public.
Your personal information is stored on a secure server. While Adolfson & Peterson Construction takes every measure to protect your information, no data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed 100% secure. Therefore, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of the information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk.
